A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1963-1964
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- General Records, 1963-1964
  - Southern Fellowships Fund (see also Council on Southern Universities) 1963-1964 (Box 32)
  - Southern Regional Education Board 1963-1964 (Box 32)
  - Southern University Conference 1963-1964 (Box 32)
  - Space Utilization 1963-1964 (Box 32)
  - Speech and Drama (folder empty) 1963-1964 (Box 32)
  - Speeches and Articles 1963-1964 (Box 32)
  - Speeches - Founder's Day - 13 April 1964 (folder empty) 1963-1964 (Box 32)
  - Speeches - Presentation of Distinguished Service Award, Virginia State Chamber of Commerce - 21 April 1964 1963-1964 (Box 32)
  - Speeches - ODK and Educational Values of Robert E. Lee - Lexington - 24 April 1964 1963-1964 (Box 32)
  - Speeches - James Monroe and Our Time - James Monroe Memorial Foundation - 27 April 1964 1963-1964 (Box 32)
  - Speeches - ODK Luncheon - 13 May 1964 (folder empty) 1963-1964 (Box 32)
  - Speeches - Charlottesville/Albemarle Chamber of Commerce - 14 May 1964 1963-1964 (Box 32)
  - Speeches - Alumni Banquet - 16 May 1964 (folder empty) 1963-1964 (Box 32)
  - Speeches - Dedication of New Dormitories - 16 May 1964 (folder empty) 1963-1964 (Box 32)
  - Speeches - "To Make a Beginning" - Commencement - Longwood College, 31 May 1964 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - "Not to Fail" - Wake Forest College Commencement, 8 June 1964 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - "Robert E. Lee and Education" - Virginians of Maryland - 18 January 1964 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - "Robert E. Lee and Education" - Virginians of Maryland - 18 January 1964 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - 30 January 1964 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges - 1 July 1963 (folder empty) 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - Remarks at Admissions Institute - 8 August 1963 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - Dedication of Hematology Research Lab named for Dean Jordan - 16 August 1963 (folder empty) 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - Summer School Graduation - 17 August 1963 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - Remarks at First Anniversary of Patrick Henry Branch - 25 September 1963 (folder empty) 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - Dedication of Hematology Research Lab named for Dean Jordan - 16 August 1963 (folder empty) 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - Summer School Graduation - 17 August 1963 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - Remarks at First Anniversary of Patrick Henry Branch - 25 September 1963 (folder empty) 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - "The University and the Business Community" - Graduate School of Business Sponsors - 16 October 1963 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - School of Education Alumni - 1 November 1963 (folder empty) 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - Virginia Library Association - 14 November 1963 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - Report to Visitors and Charlottesville Ministerial Association - 18 November 1963 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Speeches - Chattanooga Civitan - 6 December 1963 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - State Board of Education 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - State Council of Higher Education (see also Tax Study) 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - State Department of Health 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - State Universities Association (see also Association of American Universities and Land-Grant Colleges - membership in) 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Student Affairs - Individual Students (see also Fellowships and Scholarships) 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Student Aid and Placement 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Student Costs and Enrollment (Special Study) 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Student Costs and Enrollment Material for 30 January 1964 1963-1964 (Box 35)
  - Student Financial Aid Committee 1963-1964 (Box 35)
  - Summer Session 1964 1963-1964 (Box 35)
  - Summer Session 1963 1963-1964 (Box 35)
  - "T" Miscellaneous 1963-1964 (Box 35)
  - Tax Study Commission 1963-1964 (Box 35)
  - Topics, University 1963-1964 (Box 35)
  - Traffic Control 1963-1964 (Box 35)
  - "U" Miscellaneous 1963-1964 (Box 35)
  - United States Naval Academy 1963-1964 (Box 35)
  - U. S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare (see also National Defense Education Act) 1963-1964 (Box 36)
  - U. S. Department of State 1963-1964 (Box 36)
  - University Center in Virginia 1963-1964 (Box 36)
  - University Hall (see also Field House Committee) 1963-1964 (Box 36)
  - University Houses 1963-1964 (Box 36)
  - University Printing Office 1963-1964 (Box 36)
  - University Press of Virginia 1963-1964 (Box 36)
  - "V" Miscellaneous 1963-1964 (Box 36)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1963-1964 (Box 36)
  - Virginia Associated Research Center (folder empty) 1963-1964 (Box 36)
  - Virginia Education Association 1963-1964 (Box 36)
  - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges 1963-1964 (Box 36)
  - Virginia Historical Society (see also Madison Papers) 1963-1964 (Box 36)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1963-1964 (Box 36)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce 1963-1964 (Box 36)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation (see also Public Relations meeting of all fund-raising groups) 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Athletics 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Buildings and Grounds 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Educational Policy Committee 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Executive Committee 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Finance Committee 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Mary Washington College Committee 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Medical Committee 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Special Recognition Committee 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Board of Visitors, General 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Manuel (folder empty) 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Nominations for Membership 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Minutes, January 1964 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Docket, 8 February 1964 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 8 February 1964 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Docket, 18 April 1964 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 18 April 1964 1963-1964 (Box 37)
  - Visitors - Docket, 5 June 1964 1963-1964 (Box 38)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 5 June 1964 1963-1964 (Box 38)
  - Visitors - Docket, 13 June 1964 1963-1964 (Box 38)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 13 June 1964 1963-1964 (Box 38)
  - Visitors - Docket, 18 October 1963 1963-1964 (Box 38)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 18 October 1963 1963-1964 (Box 38)
  - Visitors - Docket, 14 December 1963 1963-1964 (Box 39)
  - Visitors - Docket, 14 December 1963 1963-1964 (Box 39)
  - Visitors - Bryan, Judge A. V., Rector 1963-1964 (Box 39)
  - Visitors - Martin, Dr. Walter B. 1963-1964 (Box 39)
  - "Wa - Wh" Miscellaneous 1963-1964 (Box 39)
  - "Wi - Wz" Miscellaneous 1963-1964 (Box 39)
  - Walpole Society 1963-1964 (Box 39)
  - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies 1963-1964 (Box 39)
  - Water Pollution Laboratory 1963-1964 (Box 39)
  - Women, Dean of 1963-1964 (Box 39)
  - "X - Y - Z" Miscellaneous 1963-1964 (Box 39)
  - Young Men's Christian Association (Y.M.C.A.) 1963-1964 (Box 39)